StellarFund — cross-border crowdfunding, live on Stellar mainnet.
First, connect a Stellar wallet — this is real XLM on mainnet.
Open a campaign to see its milestone timeline and progress.
Contribute real XLM — held in a smart-contract escrow, not by a middleman.
Approve the transaction; funds release only as milestones are met.
The contribution is confirmed on-chain in seconds.
Every transaction is public and verifiable on stellar.expert.
Browse campaigns across categories — Education, Health, Technology and more.
Search and filters make it easy to find a cause to support.
Now let's create a brand-new campaign, live on mainnet.
Give it an identity: title, description, category and a cover image.
Set the funding goal in XLM.
Define the milestones — each releases one tranche of funds as it's met.
The milestones must sum to the goal; this is enforced on-chain.
Submitting deploys a dedicated escrow contract through the Factory.
Sign the transaction in your wallet to confirm.
In seconds, the new campaign is live on-chain.
Here's the campaign we just created, now live on the home page.
The Proof of Users board reads real backers straight from the blockchain.
Every wallet and amount is verifiable on stellar.expert — no fake numbers.
We collect user details and feedback through a short form.
Name, email and wallet address — so each response is verifiable on-chain.
Users rate the experience and how easy it was to contribute.
They tell us what they did: connect, contribute, or create a campaign.
And what they liked most, plus what we should build next.
This feedback drives the roadmap — TTL hardening, fee sponsorship, profiles.
Real users, real transactions, real feedback — all on Stellar mainnet.
StellarFund — global funding, milestone-enforced. Thanks for watching!